A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Asia and Pacific, Office Files of Reed Hertford FA552
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Trip, Conference Files, 1976-1981; II
  - Agricultural Development Council (ADC) and International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT) Conference on Rural Labor Markets (Aug 22-24, 1979) -- Papers (3 of 3) (Box 2)
  - India -- Trip Files (Fall 1979) Re: Agriculture, Food, and Rural Development (Box 2)
  - Yogjakarta Meeting -- Asia and the Pacific Agriculture and Resources (Nov 13-17, 1979) -- Memoranda, Draft Papers (Box 2)
  - Proceedings of the Yogjakarta Conference (Nov 13-17, 1979) (1 of 2) (Box 2)
  - Proceedings of the Yogjakarta Conference (Nov 13-17, 1979) (2 of 2) (Box 2)
  - Final Papers for Yogjakarta Conference (Nov 1979) (Box 2)
  - "Food, Employment, and the Role of Women in Indonesia" (Yogjakarta conference paper and recommendation for Foundation action), 1979 (Box 2)
  - Nov 1979 -- Trip to Pakistan, Indonesia -- Yogjakarta Agriculture Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
  - Bangladesh -- Trip Report, Grant Proposals, Memoranda Re: Budget, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Colombia/Jamaica Trip, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Agriculture, Natural Resources and Related Rural Development Meeting -- Rapporteur Notes, Jun 1981 (Box 2)
- Subject Files, 1952-1981; III
  - Affirmative Action -- Report, Mar 1979 (Box 2)
  - Agricultural Research -- Englander, 1980 (Box 2)
  - American Agricultural Economics Association -- Correspondence, Memoranda, 1976-1979 (Box 2)
  - American Agricultural Economics Association (AAEA) -- Report on India and Agricultural Economics, Dec 1978 (Box 2)
  - American Agricultural Economics Association (AAEA) Surveys Re: Agricultural Economics Training, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Antique Upland Development Program -- Re: Philippines Agriculture, 1976-1979 (Box 2)
  - "Bibliography of Substantive Writings" -- The Ford Foundation India and Nepal, 1969 (Box 2)
  - "Building National Capacity to Develop Water User' Associations: Experience from the Philippines"by Frances F. Korten, Jul 27, 1981 (Box 2)
  - "Community Organization and Rural Development: A Learnng Process Approach" by David C. Korten, Apr 1980 (Box 2)
  - "Exchange Rate, Commercial Policy and Agricultural Development: The Experience of Colombia from 1953 to 1978" by Jorge Garcia Garcia (1 of 2), Sep 1980 (Box 2)
  - "Exchange Rate, Commercial Policy and Agricultural Development: The Experience of Colombia from 1953 to 1978" by Jorge Garcia Garcia (2 of 2), Sep 1980 (Box 2)
  - Food, Agriculture and Nutrition Policy and Activity -- Memoranda, Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 2)
  - "Health" Memorandum Re: Health Priorities Withing Ford Foundation International Program, Jun 13, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Irrigation and Water Management and Improvement in Southeast Asia -- Papers and Memorandum, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Files -- Agrarian Research, Resources and the Environment, Social Development, Asia Trip Files, Program Planning, etc., 1978-1981 (Box 2)
  - "Nature and Measurement of Economic Efficiency in Indian Agriculture" by R.K. Sampath, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Nutrition, Agriculture and Food Policy -- Papers, Remarks, 1978-1980 (Box 2)
  - Pakistan, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
  - "Plans for Resources and the Environment Program" -- Information Paper for the Trustee Committee on Education and Public Policy, Dec 1979 (Box 2)
  - Program Review -- Division of Education and Public Policy -- Resources and the Environment, Jan 14, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Review of Public Policy and Social Organization Program, Jan 19, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Review of Research on Women in Agriculture and Rural Development, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Rural Development, Agriculture, Labor Supply and Wages, Land Reform -- Papers/Research Funded by Ford Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - Rural Resources and Development, Women, Urban Poverty and the Disadvantaged -- Grant Proposals, Memoranda, Reports, etc., 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - "Siblings and Schooling in Urban Colombia" (dissertation researched with Ford Foundation funding) by Nancy Monica Birdsall, 1979 (Box 3)
  - "Some Observations on Ford Foundation Supported Community Development Corporations and their Significance for Implementation of Government Policies and Programs" by Sol Chafkin, Oct 1977 (Box 3)
  - "Southeast Asia-An Annotated Bibliography of Selected Reference Sources" -- Library of Congress Orientalia Division, 1952 (Box 3)
  - "Una Evaluacion de la Intervencion del Gobierno en el mercado de arroz en Colombia" by Nestor Gutierrez and Reed Hertford (in Spanish), 1974 (Box 3)
  - Working Group -- Rural Resources and Development and Women's Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 3)